thefreebiejunkie.com 2008-06-19

# Untitled Document

Privacy Policy

TheFreebieJunkie.com is committed to keeping all your personal details safe and secure. Our privacy policy strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

**Collecting Your Personal Information**

TheFreebieJunkie.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information collected about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). We will not pass on your details to any third party and do not send out marketing e-mails to customers unless they have registered to receive such material, purchased from us, or downloaded one of our free or paid products.

The type of information we ‘may’ collect about you includes:

> Your full name  
>  Your e-mail address  
>  Your postal address

Generally, this information is requested when you are either downloading free products, when you purchase any of our products (eBooks, software etc.), or when you subscribe to our newsletters. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.

The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. 

**How We Control Your Personal Information**

We will not use your personal information for any other reason other than to contact you. We do not sell, give away or rent your email address to any third party. If in the future we did for any reason wish to rent, sell or use your email address for any other purpose we will ask you for your permission first.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

Your personal information is used for four main purposes and they are as follows:

  1. To send out information, recommendations and resources to you.
  2. To provide assistance to you after you have purchased products from us.
  3. To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
  4. To enlighten you about new products, services, tool, upgrades, special offers and information which we feel may be of use to you.

We will only disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  1. Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TheFreebieJunkie.com
  2. Protect and defend the rights or property of TheFreebieJunkie.com
  3. Act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TheFreebieJunkie.com

**Children**

TheFreebieJunkie.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe TheFreebieJunkie.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

**Changes to this Policy**

TheFreebieJunkie.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.
